Consumers' League of New York City Records 5307
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Earnings of Women In Factories and a Legal Living Wage. New York: The League, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  87 p.
- The Eight Hours Day and Rest at Night by Statute. New York: The League, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  11pp
- The Eight Hours Day for Wage Earning Women. New York: The League, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  12pp
- Equal Opportunity for Women Wage Earners: Facts vs. Fiction. New York: The League, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  10pp
- The High Cost of Living and the Ten Years' Program, 1920-1930, of the National Consumers' League. New York; The League (Box 49, Folder 16)
  7pp
- Labor Laws of Twelve Southern States. New York; The League, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Manufacturers for the Minimum Wage Law, New York: The League, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  4pp
- Memorandum to the Public Service Commission of New York -First District on the Proposed Plan to Provide Fair and Reasonable Wages and Working Conditions and to Prevent Interruption of the Service on Street Railroads. New York: The League, 1917 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  16 p.
- Minimum Wage Commissions-Current Facts. New York: The League, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  15 p.
- Minimum. Wage Commissions-Current Facts. New York: The League, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Minimum Wage Commissions -Current Facts. New York: The League, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- The National Consumers' League - First Quarter Century, 1899-1924. New York: The League (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Report of the Second Annual Meeting of the Labor Standards Conference Called by the National Consumers League. New York: The League, 1933 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  18 p.
- Should the National Labor Relations Act be Amended? New York: The League, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  8p
- Standard Minimum [Living] Wage Bill. New York: The League, 1922 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  7p
- The Unstandardized Industry - Hotel: How to Standardize It. New York: The League, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- The Waste of Industry: Overworked Women and Girls (Box 49, Folder 28)
  Pamphlet missing
- Youth In Danger: A Study of Young Workers Injured In Georgia Industries. New York: The League, 1930 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  12p
- Consumers' League, New Jersey and National. Night-Working Mothers in Textile Mills - Passaic, New Jersey. Newark: The League, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  20 p.
- Consumers' League, New Orleans. Report to the Louisiana State Commission to Study the Conditions of Working Women and Children, New Orleans: The League, 1915 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  24 p.
- Consumers' League, New York City. Behind the Scenes in a Restaurant: A Study of 1017 Women Restaurant Employees. New York: The League, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  47 P.
- Campaigning Against Industrial Evils: The Report of the Consumers' League of the City of New York, 1916, New York: The League (Box 49, Folder 33)
  30 p.
- Campaigning Against Industrial Evils: The Report of the Consumers' League of the City of New York, 1917. New York: The League, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Children Who Work In the Tenements, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 34a)
  8 p.
- Historical Sketch of the Pioneer Consumers' League. New York: The League, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- How Manufacturing In Tenements Endangers Public Health and Breaks Down Family Life. New York: The League, 1917 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Is This Living?, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 36a)
- Laws Every Woman Worker Should Know. New York: The League, n.d. 6 p. (Box 49, Folder 37)
  no date, 6 p.
- Report for the Year Ending December 1914. New York: the League, 1915 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  57 p.
- Towards A New Industrial Era: The Report of the Consumers' League of the City of New York - 1918. New York: The League, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Twenty-Five Years of the Consumers' League of the City of New York. New York: The League, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  41 p.
- The Work of the Consumers' League of the City of New York -1915. New York: The League, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  28 p.
- Consumers' League, New York State. Behind the Scenes in Candy Factories. New York: The League, 1925 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  66 p.
- Behind the Scenes In Canneries. New York: The League, 1930 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  55 p.
- Behind the Scenes in a Hotel. New York: The League, 1922 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  47 p.
- The Case for Special Legislation for Women Workers. New York: The League, 1919 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  4p
- The City Migistrates and the Labor Law: Do They Respect It? New York: The League, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  14 p.
- The Community Looks at Migrant Labor. New York: The League, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Consumers' Cooperative Societies in New York State. New York: The League, 1922 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- End Feudalism on the Farms. New York: The League, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  6p
- The Forty Eight Hour Law: Do Working Women Want It? New York: The League, 1927 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  37 p.
- The Joads in New York. New York: The League, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  26 p.
- Laws Every Consumer Should Know and Make Known, New York: The League, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Laws Half a Million Girls and Women Need to Know, New York: The League, 1918 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Less Than A Living Wage. New York: The League, 1921 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  9p
- Our Working Girls - How They Do It. New York: The League, 1913 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Sweatshops in the Sun. New York: The League, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  19 p.
- What Next for New York Joads? New York: The League, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  32 p.
- What the New Cannery Code Has Done for the Women Employed in New York Canneries. New York: The League, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Consumers' League, New York State and City. Women's Wages Today: One Reason for a Legal Minimum in New York State. New York: The League, 1920 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Consumers' League, Oregon. Report of the Social Survey Committee of the Consumers' League of Oregon on the Wages, Hours and Conditions of Work and Cost and Standard of Living of Women Wage Earners in Oregon with Special Reference to Portland. Portland: T, 1913 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  82 p.
- Dahl, Mary B. Cash Sickness Compensation in Rhode Island. Providence: Consumers' League of Rhode Island, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Goldmark, Pauline. Do Children Work in the Canneries? New York: Consumers' League of the City of New York, 1907 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Goldmark, Pauline and Samuel J. Rosensohn. Memorandum Addressed to the Joint Legislative Committee Investigating the New York Public Service Commissions on the Need of Legislation Empowering the Commissions to Regulate Hours of Work and Wages of Employees, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Kelley, Florence. The Case for the Minimum Wage. New York: National Consumers' League, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Kelley, Florence and Dorothy W. Myers. Children's Compensation for Industrial Injuries: How the States Love Their Children. New York: National Consumers' League, 1927 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Kelley, Florence and Marguerite Marsh. Labor Legislation for Women and Its Effects on Earnings and Conditions of Labor. New York: National Consumers' League, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Lauder, Estelle. Pennsylvania's Rank in Workmen's Compensation Legislation. Philadelphia: Consumers' League of Eastern Pennsylvania, 1930 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Lauder, Estelle. Wanted; A Hew Deal In Place of the Racketeering in Workmen's Compensation. Philadelphia: Consumers' League of Eastern Pennsylvania, 1934 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Pugh, Grace, Vacations With Pay for Factory Workers. Consumers' League of Eastern Pennsylvania, 1923 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  34 p.
- Pugh, Grace. Working Women and Children in Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Consumers' League of Eastern Pennsylvania, 1923 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- Van Kleeck, Mary. Women and Machines. New York, Consumers' League of the City of New York, 1921 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- Watt, Robert J. A Wage and Hour Program for the States. New York: National Consumers' League, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  10p
- Agricultural Labor (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Briefs (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Bulletin, 1924-1925 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Candy (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Canneries (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Christmas Shopping (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Consumers' League (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Homework (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Hotel (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Laundry (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Laws and Legislation (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Minimum Wage (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Newsletter, 1946-1954 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Newsletter, 1955-1960 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Press Releases (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Truancy (Box 52, Folder 3)
- White List (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 52, Folder 5)